{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548311008373","data":{"timestamp":" 1548311008373"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_092308"," gameId":" 746332a5-bc45-44b9-90be-c4dc19fcbd10"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kusoma kusoma"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSOMA"," userResponse":" KUSOMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548311009351","data":{"timestamp":" 1548311009350"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_092308"," gameId":" 746332a5-bc45-44b9-90be-c4dc19fcbd10"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kusoma kusoma"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSOMA"," userResponse":" KUSOMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548311012315","data":{"timestamp":" 1548311012314"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_092308"," gameId":" 746332a5-bc45-44b9-90be-c4dc19fcbd10"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunataka macho yaone"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNATAKA"," userResponse":" KUNATAKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548311012863","data":{"timestamp":" 1548311012862"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_092308"," gameId":" 746332a5-bc45-44b9-90be-c4dc19fcbd10"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunataka macho yaone"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MACHO"," userResponse":" MACHO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548311013516","data":{"timestamp":" 1548311013515"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_092308"," gameId":" 746332a5-bc45-44b9-90be-c4dc19fcbd10"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunataka macho yaone"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAONE"," userResponse":" YAONE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548311017573","data":{"timestamp":" 1548311017573"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_092308"," gameId":" 746332a5-bc45-44b9-90be-c4dc19fcbd10"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Masikio yasikie"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MASIKIO"," userResponse":" MASIKIO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548311018497","data":{"timestamp":" 1548311018496"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_092308"," gameId":" 746332a5-bc45-44b9-90be-c4dc19fcbd10"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Masikio yasikie"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YASIKIE"," userResponse":" YASIKIE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548311022242","data":{"timestamp":" 1548311022241"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_092308"," gameId":" 746332a5-bc45-44b9-90be-c4dc19fcbd10"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na mdomo useme"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548311023026","data":{"timestamp":" 1548311023026"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_092308"," gameId":" 746332a5-bc45-44b9-90be-c4dc19fcbd10"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na mdomo useme"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MDOMO"," userResponse":" MDOMO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548311024007","data":{"timestamp":" 1548311024007"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_092308"," gameId":" 746332a5-bc45-44b9-90be-c4dc19fcbd10"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na mdomo useme"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" USEME"," userResponse":" USEME"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548311027900","data":{"timestamp":" 1548311027900"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_092308"," gameId":" 746332a5-bc45-44b9-90be-c4dc19fcbd10"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kusoma kusoma"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSOMA"," userResponse":" KUSOMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548311028875","data":{"timestamp":" 1548311028874"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_092308"," gameId":" 746332a5-bc45-44b9-90be-c4dc19fcbd10"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kusoma kusoma"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSOMA"," userResponse":" KUSOMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548311031822","data":{"timestamp":" 1548311031822"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_092308"," gameId":" 746332a5-bc45-44b9-90be-c4dc19fcbd10"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunataka macho yaone"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNATAKA"," userResponse":" KUNATAKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548311032358","data":{"timestamp":" 1548311032358"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_092308"," gameId":" 746332a5-bc45-44b9-90be-c4dc19fcbd10"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunataka macho yaone"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MACHO"," userResponse":" MACHO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548311033002","data":{"timestamp":" 1548311033002"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_092308"," gameId":" 746332a5-bc45-44b9-90be-c4dc19fcbd10"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunataka macho yaone"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAONE"," userResponse":" YAONE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548311037197","data":{"timestamp":" 1548311037197"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_092308"," gameId":" 746332a5-bc45-44b9-90be-c4dc19fcbd10"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Masikio yasikie"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MASIKIO"," userResponse":" MASIKIO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548311038131","data":{"timestamp":" 1548311038130"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_092308"," gameId":" 746332a5-bc45-44b9-90be-c4dc19fcbd10"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Masikio yasikie"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YASIKIE"," userResponse":" YASIKIE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548311041840","data":{"timestamp":" 1548311041839"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_092308"," gameId":" 746332a5-bc45-44b9-90be-c4dc19fcbd10"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na mdomo useme"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548311042623","data":{"timestamp":" 1548311042623"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_092308"," gameId":" 746332a5-bc45-44b9-90be-c4dc19fcbd10"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na mdomo useme"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MDOMO"," userResponse":" MDOMO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548311043608","data":{"timestamp":" 1548311043608"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_092308"," gameId":" 746332a5-bc45-44b9-90be-c4dc19fcbd10"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na mdomo useme"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" USEME"," userResponse":" USEME"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548311046943","data":{"timestamp":" 1548311046942"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_092308"," gameId":" 746332a5-bc45-44b9-90be-c4dc19fcbd10"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Na mdomo useme"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548311047030","data":{"timestamp":" 1548311047030"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_092308"," gameId":" 746332a5-bc45-44b9-90be-c4dc19fcbd10"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na mdomo useme"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" USEME"," userResponse":" USEME"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548311059683","data":{"timestamp":" 1548311059683"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_092308"," gameId":" c6a8f13c-a954-4103-90f7-bdfab0e794d0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kusoma kusoma"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSOMA"," userResponse":" KUSOMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548311060658","data":{"timestamp":" 1548311060658"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_092308"," gameId":" c6a8f13c-a954-4103-90f7-bdfab0e794d0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kusoma kusoma"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSOMA"," userResponse":" KUSOMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548311063611","data":{"timestamp":" 1548311063611"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_092308"," gameId":" c6a8f13c-a954-4103-90f7-bdfab0e794d0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunataka macho yaone"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNATAKA"," userResponse":" KUNATAKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548311064152","data":{"timestamp":" 1548311064151"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_092308"," gameId":" c6a8f13c-a954-4103-90f7-bdfab0e794d0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunataka macho yaone"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MACHO"," userResponse":" MACHO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548311064806","data":{"timestamp":" 1548311064805"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_092308"," gameId":" c6a8f13c-a954-4103-90f7-bdfab0e794d0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunataka macho yaone"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAONE"," userResponse":" YAONE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548311069002","data":{"timestamp":" 1548311069002"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_092308"," gameId":" c6a8f13c-a954-4103-90f7-bdfab0e794d0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Masikio yasikie"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MASIKIO"," userResponse":" MASIKIO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548311069938","data":{"timestamp":" 1548311069937"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_092308"," gameId":" c6a8f13c-a954-4103-90f7-bdfab0e794d0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Masikio yasikie"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YASIKIE"," userResponse":" YASIKIE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548311073667","data":{"timestamp":" 1548311073666"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_092308"," gameId":" c6a8f13c-a954-4103-90f7-bdfab0e794d0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na mdomo useme"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548311074451","data":{"timestamp":" 1548311074451"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_092308"," gameId":" c6a8f13c-a954-4103-90f7-bdfab0e794d0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na mdomo useme"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MDOMO"," userResponse":" MDOMO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548311075437","data":{"timestamp":" 1548311075437"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_092308"," gameId":" c6a8f13c-a954-4103-90f7-bdfab0e794d0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na mdomo useme"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" USEME"," userResponse":" USEME"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548311079350","data":{"timestamp":" 1548311079350"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_092308"," gameId":" c6a8f13c-a954-4103-90f7-bdfab0e794d0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kusoma kusoma"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSOMA"," userResponse":" KUSOMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548311080314","data":{"timestamp":" 1548311080314"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_092308"," gameId":" c6a8f13c-a954-4103-90f7-bdfab0e794d0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kusoma kusoma"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSOMA"," userResponse":" KUSOMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548311083298","data":{"timestamp":" 1548311083297"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_092308"," gameId":" c6a8f13c-a954-4103-90f7-bdfab0e794d0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunataka macho yaone"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNATAKA"," userResponse":" KUNATAKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548311083842","data":{"timestamp":" 1548311083841"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_092308"," gameId":" c6a8f13c-a954-4103-90f7-bdfab0e794d0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunataka macho yaone"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MACHO"," userResponse":" MACHO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548311084493","data":{"timestamp":" 1548311084492"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_092308"," gameId":" c6a8f13c-a954-4103-90f7-bdfab0e794d0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunataka macho yaone"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAONE"," userResponse":" YAONE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548311088675","data":{"timestamp":" 1548311088674"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_092308"," gameId":" c6a8f13c-a954-4103-90f7-bdfab0e794d0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Masikio yasikie"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MASIKIO"," userResponse":" MASIKIO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548311089613","data":{"timestamp":" 1548311089612"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_092308"," gameId":" c6a8f13c-a954-4103-90f7-bdfab0e794d0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Masikio yasikie"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YASIKIE"," userResponse":" YASIKIE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548311093325","data":{"timestamp":" 1548311093324"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_092308"," gameId":" c6a8f13c-a954-4103-90f7-bdfab0e794d0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na mdomo useme"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548311094122","data":{"timestamp":" 1548311094121"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_092308"," gameId":" c6a8f13c-a954-4103-90f7-bdfab0e794d0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na mdomo useme"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MDOMO"," userResponse":" MDOMO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548311095107","data":{"timestamp":" 1548311095107"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_092308"," gameId":" c6a8f13c-a954-4103-90f7-bdfab0e794d0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na mdomo useme"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" USEME"," userResponse":" USEME"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548311098408","data":{"timestamp":" 1548311098408"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_092308"," gameId":" c6a8f13c-a954-4103-90f7-bdfab0e794d0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Na mdomo useme"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548311098473","data":{"timestamp":" 1548311098473"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_092308"," gameId":" c6a8f13c-a954-4103-90f7-bdfab0e794d0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na mdomo useme"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" USEME"," userResponse":" USEME"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}